<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tech Support</string>
    <string name="introduct">Computer are everywhere.Every child is aware of computers.But when comes fault,it makes user frustated.
        This app is designed to handle those problem in easy way.
        <b>Hope it will help you a lot.</b></string>


    <string-array name="header_titles">
        <item>System restored not turned on</item>
        <item>PC is working too slow</item>
        <item>Uninstall programs you no longer use</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="h1_items">
        <item>Solution:Follow the steps\n\n
            1.type"creatre a restore point" in search bar\n\n
            2.In system properties window highlight the "system(Local disk c:)" drive to highlight it.\n\n
            3.Click on "Configure"\n\n
            4.Check "turn on system protection"\n\n
            5.Drag the <b>Max Usage</b> so that it is around 5GB\n\n
            6.Click Apply</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="h2_items">
        <item>1.Reduce Startup Programs\n\n
              2.Type "System configuration" into the Windows search field \n\n
              3.Open the app\n\n
              4.Click on the “Services” tab and check “Hide all Microsoft services”\n\n
              5. Now turn off the programs you don’t think you need and click apply\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="h3_items">
        <item>  1.Type “Programs and features” into the Windows search field\n\n
                2.Open the app\n\n
                3.Highlight an app you are sure you no longer need and click "Uninstall/Change"\n\n
                Find junk files and delete them to free up space\n\n
                Another way to lighten your hard drive and speed up Windows is to identify all\n\n
                the temporary junk files that apps build up on your system.\n\n
                Follow these steps:\n\n
                Type "Disk cleanup" into the Windows search field\n\n
                Open the app\n\n
                Select the drive to clean (normally c:)\n\n
                Select the files you want cleaned - if you’re unsure highlight the item\n\n
                and Windows will explain in more detail\n\n</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="laptop_titles">
        <item>Turn on Laptop Touchpad</item>
        <item>Speed up your laptop</item>
        <item>Uninstall programs you no longer use</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="laptop_h1">
         <item> Many Windows 8 laptop users have encountered the problem of their touchpad not working.\n\n
                Not too big of a problem if you have a mouse to plug in but a real annoyance
                if you travel a lot and like to use your laptop on the go. Luckily, the problem is usually
                that the trackpad is simply turned off.\n\n
                To turn it on, plug in a mouse and then follow these steps:\n\n
                Press Windows key + C\n\n
                Click on “settings” and then “change PC settings”\n\n
                Go to PC and devices > Mouse and touchpad\n\n
                Make sure Touchpad is enabled\n\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="laptop_h2">
        <item>  1.Reduce Startup Programs
                2.Type "System configuration" into the Windows search field
                3.Open the app
                4.Click on the “Services” tab and check “Hide all Microsoft services”
                5. Now turn off the programs you don’t think you need and click apply</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="laptop_h3">
         <item> 1.Type “Programs and features” into the Windows search field\n\n
                2.Open the app\n\n
                3.Highlight an app you are sure you no longer need and click "Uninstall/Change"\n\n
                Find junk files and delete them to free up space\n\n
                Another way to lighten your hard drive and speed up Windows is to identify all the\n\n
                temporary junk files that apps build up on your system.\n\n
                Follow these steps:\n\n
                Type "Disk cleanup" into the Windows search field\n\n
                Open the app\n\n
                Select the drive to clean (normally c:)\n\n
                Select the files you want cleaned - if you’re unsure highlight the item and\n\n
                Windows will explain in more detail\n\n</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="android_title">
        <item>Apps not downloading</item>
        <item>Delayed Notifiction</item>
        <item>Wifi shutting downn</item>
        <item>Apps behaving erratically</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="andorid_h1">
        <item>  Apps not downloading from the Play Store can surely play a spoilsport in the hours of need.\n\n
                Often the culprit is a set of corrupt cache.\n\n
                All you have to do is head over to the app settings and clear the cache data.
                Common-Android-Problems-Solutions  Common-Android-Problems-Solutions
                Another sure-shot alternative is to erase the Google Play store history.\n\n
                Go to settings and tap on clear local history.\n\n
                And if the above doesn’t work, you can delete the default Google\n\n
                account associated with the phone and add it again to solve the problem.\n\n</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="android_h2">
        <item>  Delayed notifications can prove to be a spoiler, especially when you are on the go.\n\n
                For instance, you can miss out on an important mail from your boss.
                One of the main reasons for delayed or no notification is the Power Saver
                option that many smartphone ROMs comes built with.\n\n
                Common-Android-Problems-Solutions\n\n
                There’s little doubt that they do a fantastic job of extending the battery life,\n\n
                but have you wondered at what costs? These ‘features’ often cuts the data\n\n
                connectivity when the phone is in sleep mode thus cutting the apps\n\n
                from their only mode of communication.\n\n</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="android_h3">
        <item> Data connectivity to a smartphone is crucial to its functioning whether it’s cellular data you are connected to
                or the Wi-Fi data. And one of the common issues while connected to Wi-Fi\n\n
                is that the data switches back to cellular network as soon as the phone goes to sleep.
                Exasperating, right?\n\n
                Common-Android-Problems-Solutions\n\n
                Worry not, this too can be fixed in a jiffy? The above issue occurs due\n\n
                to the Wi-Fi sleep policy of Android. Head over to the Advanced Wi-Fi settings\n\n
                and set the  Keep Wi-Fi on during sleep to Never. This way the switch-over never happens.\n\n
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="android_h4">
        <item>  Many a times, we come across some apps that just get aborted multiple times or a few
                which just goes on displaying ads that don’t allow you do anything else.\n\n
                Common-Android-Problems-Solutions\n\n
                A safe way out of this situation is to boot the phone in safe mode.\n\n
                Once a phone is booted into the safe mode you’ll notice that all the third party apps are disabled.\n\n
                So all you have to do is tap on the uninstall button.\n\n</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
